[Return of the Queen]
[عودة الملكة]
[Episode 9]
[الحلقة 9]
Hello, we're closed today.
مرحبًا، نحن مغلقون اليوم.
But I...
ولكن انا...
You can't go in.
لا يمكنك الدخول.
Mom,
أم،
are we here
هل نحن هنا
for the buffet again?
للبوفيه مرة أخرى؟
Xuanxuan,
شوان شوان،
I...
أنا...
brought you here today to meet someone.
أحضرتك إلى هنا اليوم لمقابلة شخص ما.
Okay?
تمام؟
Who, Mom?
من أمي؟
Just someone...
مجرد شخص ما...
very, very important.
مهم جدًا جدًا.
How important, Mom?
ما مدى أهمية ذلك يا أمي؟
Hurry! Hurry!
عجل! عجل!
Ms. Lu!
السيدة لو!
Can you and Mr. Jiang
هل يمكنك أنت والسيد جيانج
return to Mare Nubium today?
العودة إلى بحر الغيوم اليوم؟
Mr. Jiang!
السيد جيانغ!
Can I ask you 2 questions?
هل يمكنني أن أسألك سؤالين؟
Just 2 questions!
سؤالين فقط!
Mr. Jiang!
السيد جيانغ!
[Mare Nubium]
[بحر السحب]
Will the Mare Nubium inheritance case
هل ستنتقل قضية ميراث ماري نوبيوم إلى المحكمة؟
be resolved today?
سيتم حلها اليوم؟
Lu Sinan and Ye Haimeng...
لو سنان ويي هايمنغ ...
Mr. Jiang!
السيد جيانغ!
Please answer our questions!
من فضلك أجب على أسئلتنا!
Mrs. Lu, long time no see.
السيدة لو، لم نلتقي منذ وقت طويل.
Mare Nubium's been turned into this mess.
لقد تحول بحر النوبيوم إلى هذه الفوضى.
I'm sure you'd rather not see me at all.
أنا متأكد من أنك تفضل عدم رؤيتي على الإطلاق.
None of us wanted things
لم يرغب أحد منا في أي شيء
to turn out this way between our families.
لتتحول الأمور بين عائلاتنا إلى هذا الحد.
Yuezhi and Bochen
يوزهي وبوخن
have always tried to reason with Haimeng.
لقد حاولت دائمًا أن أجادل مع هايمينج.
But she...
لكنها...
she's too strong-willed.
إنها قوية الإرادة للغاية.
As her uncle and aunt,
كعمها وخالتها،
it's not proper for us to say too much.
ليس من المناسب لنا أن نقول الكثير.
Is it that it's not proper
هل هذا ليس صحيحا
or that you have no right at all?
أم أنه ليس لك أي حق على الإطلاق؟
What do you mean by that, Ms. Lu?
ماذا تقصدين بذلك يا آنسة لو؟
I'm mocking you.
انا اسخر منك
You...
أنت...
Enough!
كافٍ!
Today is not the day for falling out.
اليوم ليس اليوم المناسب للخلاف.
The media outside released a statement,
وأصدرت وسائل الإعلام الخارجية بيانا،
and the board inside is prepared.
واللوحة الموجودة بداخلها جاهزة.
Whether Sinan's inheritance
هل ميراث سنان
can be transferred smoothly,
يمكن نقلها بسلاسة،
whether you, Ye Yuezhi,
سواء كنت، يي Yuezhi،
can return to your position—
يمكنك العودة إلى وضعك—
it all comes down to today.
كل هذا يعود إلى اليوم.
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
But I'm afraid it won't be that easy.
لكن أخشى أن الأمر لن يكون بهذه السهولة.
So,
لذا،
you two
انتما الاثنان
had better be clear-minded.
من الأفضل أن تكون واضح الذهن.
Don't forget
لا تنسى
those things you want to bury.
تلك الأشياء التي تريد دفنها.
Here we go again.
نحن نعيد الكَرَّة مرة أخرى.
You're Sinan's only sister.
أنت أخت سنان الوحيدة.
You should present a flower.
ينبغي عليك تقديم زهرة.
I'm not the only child
أنا لست الطفل الوحيد
of the Lu family.
من عائلة لو.
Where's Lu Siyu?
أين لو سييو؟
Siyu is locked up at home.
سييو محبوسة في المنزل.
It's better he doesn't show up on an occasion like this.
من الأفضل أن لا يظهر في مناسبة كهذه.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Today marks the fourth anniversary
اليوم يصادف الذكرى الرابعة
[Mare Nubium]
[بحر السحب]
of the death of Mr. Lu Sinan,
وفاة السيد لو سينان،
the son-in-law of Mr. Ye Mingzhi,
صهر السيد يي مينجزي،
the former chairman
الرئيس السابق
of Mare Nubium Hotel Group.
من مجموعة فنادق ماري نوبيوم.
On this occasion, the legal teams
وفي هذه المناسبة، قامت الفرق القانونية
of the Ye and Lu families
من عائلتي يي ولو
will announce the inheritance matters
سيتم الإعلان عن أمور الميراث
following Mr. Lu's death.
بعد وفاة السيد لو.
Pursuant to our clients' petition,
وفقًا لطلب عملائنا،
we have submitted to the court
لقد قدمنا ​​للمحكمة
the inheritance partition lawsuit for the estate
دعوى تقسيم الميراث للتركة
of Ye Haimeng and Lu Sinan.
يي هايمينج ولو سينان.
Pending
قيد الانتظار
the court's final judgment,
الحكم النهائي للمحكمة،
the 37% jointly held shares
37% من الأسهم المملوكة بشكل مشترك
of the couple
من الزوجين
will be frozen.
سيتم تجميدها.
However, according to
ومع ذلك، وفقا ل
the property custody agreement,
اتفاقية حضانة الممتلكات،
during the freeze period,
خلال فترة التجميد،
the Lu family will exercise custodianship
ستمارس عائلة لو الوصاية
over all inherited assets.
على جميع الأصول الموروثة.
The Lu family has signed a joint agreement
وقعت عائلة لو اتفاقية مشتركة
with nearly half of the shareholders
مع ما يقرب من نصف المساهمين
[Mare Nubium]
[بحر السحب]
of Mare Nubium.
من بحر السحاب.
Theoretically, the Lu family now controls
من الناحية النظرية، تسيطر عائلة لو الآن
over 51%
أكثر من 51%
of the equity shares.
من أسهم حقوق الملكية.
In accordance with the Company Law
وفقا لقانون الشركات
and the rules
والقواعد
of Mare Nubium Hotel Group,
من مجموعة فنادق ماري نوبيوم،
the board of directors announces—
يعلن مجلس الإدارة-
The board of directors has confirmed
وقد أكد مجلس الإدارة
the Lu family and Changlu Capital Group
عائلة لو ومجموعة تشانغلو كابيتال
have become the largest controlling shareholder
أصبحوا أكبر مساهم مسيطر
of Mare Nubium.
من بحر السحاب.
Supreme executive authority of the group has returned to the Lu family!
السلطة التنفيذية العليا للمجموعة عادت إلى عائلة لو!
[Mare Nubium]
[بحر السحب]
What's their problem?
ما هي مشكلتهم؟
Are they dissatisfied with us?
هل هم غير راضين عنا؟
At a time like this,
في وقت كهذا،
can you please use your brain?
هل يمكنك استخدام عقلك من فضلك؟
You even dare talk to me like that
حتى أنك تجرؤ على التحدث معي بهذه الطريقة
on an occasion like this?
في مناسبة كهذه؟
♪ Out of my mind ♪
♪ خارج عن عقلي ♪
♪ I've been high and low ♪
♪ لقد كنت في أعلى وأسفل ♪
♪ Fighting shadows below ♪
♪ قتال الظلال في الأسفل ♪
♪ They are invisible ♪
♪إنهم غير مرئيين ♪
♪ Out of my mind ♪
♪ خارج عن عقلي ♪
♪ I've been high and low ♪
♪ لقد كنت في أعلى وأسفل ♪
♪ Now you set me free ♪
♪ الآن حررتني ♪
♪ Brought the devil out of me ♪
♪ أخرج الشيطان مني ♪
Ye Haimeng,
يي هايمنغ،
today is Lu Sinan's funeral
اليوم جنازة لو سينان
and the confirmation
والتأكيد
of Mare Nubium's controlling shareholder.
من المساهم المسيطر في شركة Mare Nubium.
If you have something to say,
إذا كان لديك شيئا لتقوله،
say it openly.
قلها بصراحة.
This is my husband's funeral.
هذه جنازة زوجي.
Of course I'm here to speak openly.
بالطبع أنا هنا لأتحدث بصراحة.
As Lu Sinan's wife
كزوجة لو شينان
and the co-owner of nearly 37%
والمالك المشارك لحوالي 37٪
of Mare Nubium's shares,
من أسهم شركة ماري نوبيوم،
I firmly oppose the freeze.
أنا أعارض التجميد بشدة.
I am the rightful owner
أنا المالك الشرعي
of the marital assets.
من الأصول الزوجية.
I knew Ye Haimeng
أنا أعرف يي هايمنغ
wouldn't let this go easily.
لن أسمح لهذا الأمر بالمرور بسهولة.
Now this is the big news
الآن هذا هو الخبر الكبير
we've been waiting for.
لقد كنا ننتظر.
The Lu family has always wanted to take the shares
كانت عائلة لو ترغب دائمًا في الحصول على الأسهم
just because of their eldest son.
فقط بسبب ابنهم الأكبر.
But that's simply not acceptable.
ولكن هذا غير مقبول على الإطلاق.
This inheritance dispute
هذا النزاع على الميراث
is getting more complicated.
أصبح الأمر أكثر تعقيدًا.
You need evidence to support your words.
تحتاج إلى أدلة لدعم كلماتك.
The Lu family has
عائلة لو لديها
the property custody agreement
اتفاقية حضانة الممتلكات
signed by you and Lu Sinan.
تم التوقيع من قبلك ومن قبل لو سينان.
According to the deceased's will,
وفقا لوصية المتوفى،
these assets
هذه الأصول
should remain with the Lu family.
ينبغي أن يبقى مع عائلة لو.
Why do you know so much
لماذا تعرف الكثير؟
about the Lu family's affairs?
حول شؤون عائلة لو؟
I...
أنا...
As an executive director,
بصفتي مديرا تنفيذيا،
you must be aware
يجب أن تكون على علم
privately colluding with business rivals,
التواطؤ بشكل خاص مع المنافسين التجاريين،
illegally organizing board alliances,
تنظيم تحالفات مجالس إدارة بشكل غير قانوني،
and even stealing important company seal and certificate
وحتى سرقة ختم الشركة وشهادتها المهمة
carry serious consequences. Right?
تحمل عواقب وخيمة. أليس كذلك؟
Stealing company seal and certificate?
سرقة ختم الشركة والشهادة؟
Don't you dare throw all that dirty water
لا تجرؤ على رمي كل تلك المياه القذرة
at me.
عندي.
Three weeks ago,
منذ ثلاثة اسابيع،
the company seal and certificate were stolen.
تمت سرقة ختم الشركة والشهادة.
That same day,
في نفس اليوم،
Director Xia, you made a total of 12 calls
المدير شيا، لقد أجريت ما مجموعه 12 مكالمة
to the Secretary's Office.
إلى مكتب السكرتير.
In your communication records,
في سجلات اتصالاتك،
you were found
لقد تم العثور عليك
providing escape funds and a vehicle
توفير أموال الهروب والسيارة
to the other party.
إلى الطرف الآخر.
How do you have
كيف حالك
my call records?
سجلات مكالماتي؟
They must be forged!
يجب أن تكون مزورة!
The company has reported to the police.
وقد أبلغت الشركة الشرطة.
If you have any explanation,
إذا كان لديك أي تفسير،
tell it to the police.
أخبر الشرطة بذلك.
I...
أنا...
Haimeng.
هايمنغ.
Your aunt and I—
عمتك وأنا
we didn't do anything.
لم نفعل شيئا.
Hand over the agreement you signed
تسليم الاتفاقية التي وقعتها
with the Lu family.
مع عائلة لو.
Agreement? What agreement?
اتفاق؟ أي اتفاق؟
The Ye family's shares
أسهم عائلة يي
must stay with the Ye family.
يجب أن يبقى مع عائلة يي.
Ye Haimeng!
أيها هايمنغ!
Stop throwing your weight around here.
توقف عن إلقاء وزنك هنا.
At the last public funeral,
في الجنازة العامة الأخيرة،
we gave in to you.
لقد استسلمنا لك.
Do you think this time,
هل تعتقد هذه المرة،
we'll still be afraid of you?
هل سنظل خائفين منك؟
In our Lu family,
في عائلتنا لو،
you're nothing but an expelled,
أنت لست سوى مطرود
unwanted daughter-in-law.
زوجة ابن غير مرغوب فيها.
Let me finish.
دعني أنهي.
Don't think that by taking
لا تظن أنه من خلال اتخاذ
my brother's death certificate,
شهادة وفاة أخي،
you can steal
يمكنك السرقة
my brother's inheritance.
ميراث أخي.
Mare Nubium and Cloud Manor
بحر السحب وقصر السحاب
both belong to my brother.
كلاهما ينتميان إلى أخي.
And why are you still alive
ولماذا مازلت على قيد الحياة
when he's dead?
عندما يموت؟
You're his murderer, aren't you?
أنت قاتله، أليس كذلك؟
Speaking of murderers—
بالحديث عن القتلة-
Ke,
متى،
where's my car's repair record?
أين سجل إصلاح سيارتي؟
Here.
هنا.
[Vehicle Maintenance Service Receipt]
[إيصال خدمة صيانة السيارة]
Two months ago,
منذ شهرين،
I just moved into Cloud Manor.
لقد انتقلت للتو إلى Cloud Manor.
One night,
ليلة واحدة،
my car was deliberately sabotaged.
لقد تم تخريب سيارتي عمدًا.
Not only were the brakes tampered with,
لم يتم العبث بالفرامل فحسب،
[Vehicle Maintenance Service Receipt]
[إيصال خدمة صيانة السيارة]
but it was also set to accelerate past 100 km/h.
ولكن تم ضبطها أيضًا للتسارع إلى ما يزيد عن 100 كم / ساعة.
If I had been in that car that day,
لو كنت في تلك السيارة ذلك اليوم،
do you think I could make it back alive
هل تعتقد أنني سأتمكن من العودة حيًا؟
or I'd die for sure?
أو سأموت بالتأكيد؟
What does your car
ماذا تفعل سيارتك
have to do with me?
هل لي علاقة بي؟
My car
سيارتي
showed clear signs of sabotage.
وأظهرت علامات واضحة للتخريب.
That person...
هذا الشخص...
Ms. Ye.
السيدة يي
Even though there's evidence
على الرغم من وجود أدلة
to prove your car was sabotaged,
لإثبات أن سيارتك تعرضت للتخريب،
it has nothing to do with Siyue.
ليس له علاقة بسيوي.
She's the young lady of the Lu family.
إنها الفتاة الشابة من عائلة لو.
She's never even had
لم يكن لديها حتى
to lift a finger.
رفع إصبع.
How could she possibly
كيف يمكنها ذلك؟
sabotage your car's braking system?
تخريب نظام الفرامل في سيارتك؟
The young lady of the Lu family wouldn't,
لن تفعل الشابة من عائلة لو ذلك،
but someone around her...
ولكن شخص ما حولها...
might.
قد.
Three years ago,
منذ ثلاث سنوات،
Ms. Ye Haimeng's mother,
والدة السيدة يي هايمينج،
Ms. Luo Yanxin,
السيدة لوه يانكسين،
was secretly sent
تم إرساله سرا
to a private sanatorium.
إلى مصحة خاصة.
Her health continued to deteriorate.
واستمرت صحتها في التدهور.
On the night of the 12th last month,
في ليلة الثاني عشر من الشهر الماضي،
she unfortunately died all of a sudden.
لقد ماتت للأسف فجأة.
So,
لذا،
we conducted a detailed investigation.
لقد أجرينا تحقيقًا مفصلاً.
We found that that very afternoon,
لقد وجدنا أنه في نفس بعد الظهر،
Mr. Jiang Lin, the husband of the Lu family's daughter,
السيد جيانج لين، زوج ابنة عائلة لو،
Lu Siyue,
لو سيوي,
left the sanatorium in a hurry
غادر المصحة على عجل
just 10 minutes
10 دقائق فقط
after Ms. Luo Yanxin's death.
بعد وفاة السيدة لوه يانكسين.
[To the Inpatient Building]
[إلى مبنى المرضى الداخليين]
Impossible!
مستحيل!
This must be fake!
لابد أن يكون هذا مزيفًا!
You must have used
يجب أن تكون قد استخدمت
AI technology
تكنولوجيا الذكاء الاصطناعي
to fabricate this!
لصنع هذا!
Jiang Lin was out handling business that day.
كان جيانج لين خارجًا للتعامل مع الأعمال في ذلك اليوم.
He couldn't possibly be at the sanatorium!
من غير الممكن أن يكون موجودًا في المصحة!
It wasn't me.
لم أكن أنا.
I didn't do anything.
لم أفعل شيئا.
I didn't kill anyone!
لم أقتل أحدا!
In the face of evidence,
في مواجهة الأدلة،
explanations are meaningless.
التفسيرات ليس لها معنى.
Jie.
هم.
Take Jiang Lin and Director Xia outside.
خذ جيانج لين والمدير شيا إلى الخارج.
Hand them over to the police.
سلمهم للشرطة.
Don't touch my husband!
لا تلمس زوجي!
Stop it!
اوقفها!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Jiang Lin!
جيانغ لين!
Siyue.
سيوي.
Siyue!
سييو!
Jiang Lin!
جيانغ لين!
Mom!
أم!
Ms. Ye, let me explain! Ms. Ye!
آنسة يي، دعيني أشرح! آنسة يي!
Jiang Lin!
جيانغ لين!
Siyue.
سيوي.
Siyue!
سييو!
Jiang Lin!
جيانغ لين!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Mom!
أم!
Jiang Lin!
جيانغ لين!
Ms. Chang, it's done?
السيدة تشانج، هل تم ذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
This is the expedited judicial authentication report.
هذا هو تقرير المصادقة القضائية السريعة.
When you arrive,
عندما تصل،
give it to Ye Haimeng and let her unseal it personally.
أعطيها إلى Ye Haimeng ودعها تفتحها شخصيًا.
Only she can unseal it?
هل هي وحدها القادرة على فتحه؟
Okay.
تمام.
I'll give it to her personally.
سأعطيها لها شخصيا.
Siyue!
سييو!
Jiang Lin!
جيانغ لين!
Mom!
أم!
Ms. Ye, let me explain! Ms. Ye!
آنسة يي، دعيني أشرح! آنسة يي!
Stop it!
اوقفها!
Let go!
اتركه!
I've got it, Bochen.
لقد حصلت عليه، بوخن.
Let's go to Mare Nubium.
دعنا نذهب إلى بحر السحاب.
Siyu,
سيو،
why don't you...
لماذا لا تفعل...
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Why don't you let me deliver it for you?
لماذا لا تسمح لي بتسليمه لك؟
Didn't we promise
ألم نعد؟
Ye Haimeng and Ling Ke
يي هايمينج ولينغ كي
that we'd get the authentication report?
هل سنحصل على تقرير المصادقة؟
Besides, I promised Ye Haimeng
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، لقد وعدت يي هايمينج
that I would personally be there.
أني سأكون هناك شخصياً.
She asked you to deliver it yourself?
لقد طلبت منك توصيلها بنفسك؟
Yes.
نعم.
What are you thinking about, Bochen?
ماذا تفكر فيه يا بوخن؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Mom.
أم.
Jiang Lin was taken away by them.
لقد تم أخذ جيانج لين بعيدًا عنهم.
You can't just sit here and do nothing!
لا يمكنك فقط الجلوس هنا وعدم فعل أي شيء!
Ye Haimeng,
يي هايمنغ،
I'm truly impressed.
أنا معجب حقا.
But
لكن
does any of this change the fact
هل أي من هذا يغير الحقيقة؟
that you and Sinan were once married?
أنك وسنان كنتما متزوجين في السابق؟
Can it make
هل يمكن أن يصنع
all the inheritance Sinan left behind
كل الميراث الذي تركه سنان خلفه
fall entirely into your hands?
تقع بالكامل بين يديك؟
Stop dreaming.
توقف عن الحلم.
[Property Custody Agreement]
[اتفاقية حراسة الممتلكات]
This property custody agreement
اتفاقية حضانة الممتلكات هذه
left by Sinan is
تركها سنان
your fatal weakness.
ضعفك القاتل.
You want to use
تريد استخدام
this property custody agreement
اتفاقية حضانة الممتلكات هذه
to threaten me,
لتهديدي،
don't you?
أنت , لا؟
[Property Custody Agreement]
[اتفاقية حراسة الممتلكات]
This is the property custody agreement
هذه هي اتفاقية حضانة الممتلكات
left by Mr. Lu Sinan,
تركها السيد لو سينان،
the eldest son of the Lu family.
الابن الأكبر لعائلة لو.
The agreement bears the signatures
الاتفاقية تحمل التوقيعات
of both Mr. Lu Sinan
من كلا السيدين لو سينان
and Ms. Ye Haimeng.
والسيدة يي هايمنغ.
Ms. Ye agreed to assign
وافقت السيدة يي على التعيين
their jointly held assets
أصولهم المشتركة
to the Lu family.
إلى عائلة لو.
Ye Haimeng!
أيها هايمنغ!
You think you can take all of Mare Nubium
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع أن تأخذ كل بحر النوبة؟
with just this piece of paper?
فقط بهذه القطعة من الورق؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Everyone,
الجميع،
the signatures
التوقيعات
of Mr. Lu Sinan
للسيد لو سينان
and Ms. Ye Haimeng
والسيدة يي هايمنغ
on this property custody agreement
بشأن اتفاقية حضانة هذه الممتلكات
are forgeries.
هي مزورة.
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
The paper source of this agreement
المصدر الورقي لهذه الاتفاقية
is a high-end luxury hotel in Europe,
هو فندق فاخر وراقي في أوروبا،
but the ink on the paper
لكن الحبر على الورق
originates domestically.
نشأ محليا.
We have sampled and analyzed
لقد قمنا بأخذ العينات وتحليلها
the ink brand
علامة الحبر
used on the agreement.
المستخدمة في الاتفاقية.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
it matches exactly the ink brand
إنه يتطابق تمامًا مع العلامة التجارية للحبر
used in the printers...
المستخدمة في الطابعات...
of Mare Nubium's Secretary's Office.
مكتب سكرتير ماري نوبيوم.
The agreement was reprinted?
هل تمت إعادة طباعة الاتفاقية؟
Did they conduct a trace analysis?
هل أجروا تحليل الأثر؟
They even analyzed the ink composition.
حتى أنهم قاموا بتحليل تركيبة الحبر.
The opposing lawyer—
المحامي المعارض—
Looks like...
يبدو مثل...
Is a reprinted document
هي وثيقة أعيد طباعتها
valid?
صالح؟
Stop spreading rumors.
اتوقفوا عن نشر الشائعات
You can't just randomly pick an ink brand
لا يمكنك اختيار علامة تجارية للحبر بشكل عشوائي
and claim the agreement is invalid.
ويدعي أن الاتفاقية غير صالحة.
Are you joking?
هل انت تمزح؟
I never signed
لم أوقع أبدا
this document.
هذه الوثيقة.
It was your eldest son, Lu Sinan,
لقد كان ابنك الأكبر، لو سينان،
who imitated my handwriting
من قلد خط يدي
and forged
ومزورة
this property custody agreement.
اتفاقية حضانة الممتلكات هذه.
The signatures were forged by Lu Sinan?
هل تم تزوير التوقيعات من قبل لو سينان؟
Then the agreement shouldn't be valid.
ومن ثم فإن الاتفاق لا ينبغي أن يكون صالحا.
The agreement is invalid?
الاتفاقية غير صالحة؟
The management rights of the inheritance
حقوق إدارة الميراث
should not remain with the Lu family then.
لا ينبغي أن يبقى مع عائلة لو إذن.
Ye Haimeng,
يي هايمنغ،
I never thought you'd go this far.
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أنك ستذهب إلى هذا الحد.
Just to take all of Mare Nubium,
فقط لأخذ كل بحر النوبيوم،
you first claimed the Lu family
لقد ادعيت أولاً أن لديك عائلة لو
bullied you,
لقد تنمر عليك
and now you're even framing
والآن أنت حتى تقوم بالتأطير
your dead husband,
زوجك المتوفى
Lu Sinan!
أنت هناك!
Open your eyes
افتح عينيك
right now!
الآن!
Open them wide!
افتحهم على مصراعيهم!
Look at your husband!
أنظري إلى زوجك!
Look at Lu Sinan
انظر إلى لو سينان
and say he
ويقول هو
forged your signatures!
تزوير توقيعاتك!
Say he
قل هو
wanted to steal your assets!
أراد سرقة أصولك!
Say it!
قلها!
You forced me to do this.
لقد أجبرتني على فعل هذا.
What are you going to do now?
ماذا ستفعل الآن؟
Lu Siyu.
لو سيو.
Come in.
ادخل.
I've got the authentication report.
لقد حصلت على تقرير المصادقة.
Lu Siyu, do you even remember your surname is Lu?
لو سي يو، هل تتذكرين أن لقبك هو لو؟
Do you have to tear the Lu family apart
هل يجب عليك تمزيق عائلة لو؟
before you're satisfied?
قبل أن تشعر بالرضا؟
[Mare Nubium]
[بحر السحب]
Haimeng.
هايمنغ.
This is the youngest son of the Lu family,
هذا هو الابن الأصغر لعائلة لو،
Lu Sinan's biological brother.
الأخ البيولوجي للو سينان.
He personally brought
لقد أحضر شخصيا
[Handwriting Authentication Report]
[تقرير مصادقة خط اليد]
the handwriting authentication report.
تقرير التحقق من خط اليد.
The report states:
وجاء في التقرير:
after comparative signature verification,
بعد التحقق من التوقيع المقارن،
the signatures on the custody agreement
التوقيعات على اتفاقية الحضانة
of both parties
من كلا الطرفين
were written by the same person.
تمت كتابتها بواسطة نفس الشخص.
So the signatures were really forged
لذا فإن التوقيعات كانت مزورة بالفعل
by Lu Sinan?
بقلم لو سينان؟
The agreement must be invalid.
يجب أن تكون الاتفاقية غير صالحة.
The agreement is invalid?
الاتفاقية غير صالحة؟
Then Lu Sinan's inheritance
ثم ميراث لو سينان
shouldn't remain with the Lu family.
لا ينبغي أن يبقى مع عائلة لو.
Ye Haimeng,
يي هايمنغ،
how dare you use
كيف تجرؤ على استخدام
Lu Siyu!
لو سيو!
I told you long ago
لقد قلت لك منذ زمن طويل
this woman has ill intentions.
هذه المرأة لديها نوايا سيئة.
She's been using you to harm the Lu family!
لقد كانت تستخدمك لإيذاء عائلة لو!
Is this...
هذا هو...
why you insisted
لماذا أصريت
I show up here?
هل اظهر هنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
I want to tell the Lu family
أريد أن أخبر عائلة لو
the property custody agreement
اتفاقية حضانة الممتلكات
left by Lu Sinan
تركها لو سينان
is completely fake.
هو مزيف تماما.
[Mare Nubium]
[بحر السحب]
I'll take back the shares
سأستعيد الأسهم
of Mare Nubium.
من بحر السحاب.
I will also take back
سأستعيدها أيضًا
the property use rights of Cloud Manor.
حقوق استخدام الملكية الخاصة بـ Cloud Manor.
The property deed of Cloud Manor?
سند ملكية Cloud Manor؟
How did you get it?
كيف حصلت عليه؟
[Real Estate Ownership Certificate of the People's Republic of China]
[شهادة ملكية العقارات لجمهورية الصين الشعبية]
You don't really think
أنت لا تعتقد ذلك حقا
that when you were
أنك عندما كنت
going after Haimeng back then,
الذهاب وراء هايمينج في ذلك الوقت،
we didn't have a backup plan, do you?
لم يكن لدينا خطة احتياطية، أليس كذلك؟
[Real Estate Ownership Certificate of the People's Republic of China]
[شهادة ملكية العقارات لجمهورية الصين الشعبية]
[Location:]
[موقع:]
[No. 116 Wutong Road, Phoenix Street, Xiangyun District, Haijiang City]
[رقم 116 طريق ووتونغ، شارع فينيكس، منطقة شيانغيون، مدينة هايجيانغ]
You dared to steal from my room!
لقد تجرأت على السرقة من غرفتي!
[Real Estate Ownership Certificate of the People's Republic of China]
[شهادة ملكية العقارات لجمهورية الصين الشعبية]
The owner listed on the property deed is
المالك المدرج في سند الملكية هو
Ms. Ye Haimeng.
السيدة يي هايمنغ.
Taking back what belongs to her—
استعادة ما ينتمي لها
how is that stealing?
كيف تعتبر هذه سرقة؟
As the president of Mare Nubium,
بصفتي رئيسًا لشركة Mare Nubium،
I officially announce
أعلن رسميا
Lu Sinan, who married me
لو سينان الذي تزوجني
4 years ago,
منذ 4 سنوات،
has passed away in a car accident.
توفي في حادث سيارة.
Mare Nubium's shares
أسهم بحر الغيوم
he obtained through marriage
حصل عليه عن طريق الزواج
will be fully reclaimed under my name.
سيتم استعادتها بالكامل تحت اسمي.
The real estate assets, including Cloud Manor,
الأصول العقارية، بما في ذلك Cloud Manor،
that we jointly purchased
التي اشتريناها بشكل مشترك
will also be reclaimed.
سيتم استعادتها أيضًا.
I will hold the largest actual controlling stake
سأحمل أكبر حصة سيطرة فعلية
in Mare Nubium.
في بحر السحاب.
Senior executives and employees
كبار المديرين والموظفين
who should not remain in the group
من لا ينبغي أن يبقى في المجموعة
and individuals who should not remain
والأفراد الذين لا ينبغي أن يبقوا
in Cloud Manor
في كلاود مانور
will all be removed.
سيتم إزالة كافة.
From today onwards,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
I'll be the largest shareholder
سأكون المساهم الأكبر
of Mare Nubium
بحر السحب
and the absolute controlling party
والطرف المسيطر المطلق
[Mare Nubium]
[بحر السحب]
of Mare Nubium's board of directors.
من مجلس إدارة شركة ماري نوبيوم.
♪ Out of my mind ♪
♪ خارج عن عقلي ♪
♪ I've been high and low ♪
♪ لقد كنت في أعلى وأسفل ♪
♪ Fighting shadows below ♪
♪ قتال الظلال في الأسفل ♪
♪ They are invisible ♪
♪إنهم غير مرئيين ♪
♪ Everywhere in my life ♪
♪ في كل مكان في حياتي ♪
[No smoking]
[ممنوع التدخين]
♪ A horrible dream ♪
♪ حلم مروع ♪
♪ I've never understood ♪
♪ لم أفهم أبدًا ♪
♪ What exactly we are ♪
♪ ما نحن عليه بالضبط ♪
♪ Felt a voice in me ♪
♪ شعرت بصوت في داخلي ♪
♪ Reaching up from deep ♪
♪ الوصول من الأعماق ♪
♪ And it's catching fire ♪
♪ وهي تشتعل ♪
♪ Nowhere left to hide ♪
♪ لم يتبق مكان للاختباء ♪
♪ Finally ♪
♪ أخيرا ♪
Haimeng.
هايمنغ.
Does it have to be like this?
هل يجب أن يكون الأمر هكذا؟
This is the Lu family's choice.
هذا هو اختيار عائلة لو.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I know in your heart,
أنا أعلم في قلبك،
you must blame me.
يجب عليك أن تلومني.
The promises I made to you
الوعود التي قطعتها لك
in the study—
في الدراسة—
I failed to keep every single one.
لقد فشلت في الحفاظ على كل واحدة منها.
I failed to restrain
لقد فشلت في كبح جماح
my wife
.زوجتي
and my children.
وأولادي.
I failed to hand over Mare Nubium or Cloud Manor
لقد فشلت في تسليم Mare Nubium أو Cloud Manor
to you too.
لك أيضا.
It's all my fault.
إنه خطئي كله.
I got them back
لقد استعدتهم
on my own anyway.
بمفردي على أية حال.
So you mean...
فهل تقصد...
you can't forgive me?
لا يمكنك أن تسامحني؟
Haimeng,
هايمنغ،
you're a daughter-in-law
أنت زوجة ابني
accepted by the entire Lu family.
تم قبولها من قبل عائلة لو بأكملها.
I remember on your wedding day,
أتذكر في يوم زفافك،
your father personally placed your hand
لقد وضع والدك يدك شخصيًا
into Sinan's,
إلى سنان،
entrusting you to our Lu family.
نعهدك إلى عائلة لو.
At that time, I told myself
في ذلك الوقت قلت لنفسي
no matter what happens
مهما حدث
in this life,
في هذه الحياة،
you will always be my daughter.
سوف تظلين ابنتي دائمًا.
Haven't you seen the media reports?
ألم تشاهدوا التقارير الإعلامية؟
Lu Sinan's funeral is
جنازة لو سينان
already over.
لقد انتهى بالفعل.
My surname is Ye.
لقبي هو يي.
Haimeng,
هايمنغ،
do you really have to sever all ties
هل يجب عليك حقا قطع جميع العلاقات؟
with the Lu family?
مع عائلة لو؟
At my age,
في عمري،
I thought losing a son was the greatest pain.
اعتقدت أن فقدان ابني هو أعظم الألم.
I never imagined I'd end up facing
لم أتخيل أبدًا أنني سأواجه
the hatred of old friends
كراهية الأصدقاء القدامى
and in-laws.
والأصهار.
I always believed
لقد اعتقدت دائما
that the Ye and Lu families
أن عائلتي يي ولو
would never come to this.
لن أصل إلى هذا أبدًا.
And we wouldn't become a spectacle
ولن نصبح مشهدًا
over the mere shares
على مجرد الأسهم
between you and Sinan.
بينك وبين سنان.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
You're the head of the Ye family now.
أنت رئيس عائلة يي الآن.
Since you've said it yourself,
بما أنك قلت ذلك بنفسك،
the Ye and Lu families
عائلتا يي ولو
will part ways from now on.
سوف نفترق من الآن فصاعدا.
I'll take the Lu family
سوف آخذ عائلة لو
and move out of Cloud Manor.
والخروج من Cloud Manor.
Chen Mo.
تشين مو.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Ke.
متى.
Haimeng.
هايمنغ.
Everything is ready.
كل شئ جاهز .
Shall we begin now?
هل نبدأ الآن؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
[Cloud Manor]
[قصر السحاب]
My necklaces.
قلاداتي.
My jewelry.
مجوهراتي.
My brother's trophies.
جوائز أخي.
And his arrow case.
وحقيبة سهمه.
How dare you throw them!
كيف تجرؤ على رميهم!
If they break, can you even afford to compensate?
إذا انكسرت، هل يمكنك تحمل تكاليف التعويض؟
[Cloud Manor]
[قصر السحاب]
You can make us move out,
يمكنك أن تجعلنا نتحرك للخارج،
but why throw our things?
ولكن لماذا نرمي أغراضنا؟
If anything is broken,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء مكسور،
can you afford to pay for it?
هل تستطيع تحمل تكاليف ذلك؟
Mom.
أم.
Look at that Ye Haimeng.
أنظر إلى ذلك يي هايمينج.
We were too soft on her.
لقد كنا متساهلين معها للغاية.
Back when she insisted on moving in,
عندما أصرت على الانتقال،
we should have
كان ينبغي علينا
thrown her out too!
طردتها أيضا!
Look at her now,
أنظر إليها الآن،
so arrogant just because she won.
متغطرسة جدًا فقط لأنها فازت.
She threw my jewelry
لقد رمت مجوهراتي
and all my belongings!
وكل متعلقاتي!
You actually have the nerve to come back!
لديك الشجاعة للعودة فعلا!
This is all your fault.
كل هذا خطؤك .
You sided with an outsider
لقد انحازت إلى شخص خارجي
instead of your own family.
بدلا من عائلتك.
You insisted on helping that woman.
لقد أصريت على مساعدة تلك المرأة.
What did she even offer you?
ماذا عرضت عليك حتى؟
What kind of spell did she cast on you?
ما نوع التعويذة التي ألقتها عليك؟
She winked at you,
لقد غمزت لك
and you just ran towards her?
وركضت نحوها؟
Lu Siyu, she's your brother's wife.
لو سي يو، إنها زوجة أخيك.
She's your sister-in-law!
إنها أخت زوجك!
You actually believed her!
لقد صدقتها فعلا!
You jerk! You...
يا أحمق! أنت...
Mom.
أم.
You're not allowed to come home.
ليس مسموح لك بالعودة إلى المنزل.
The Lu family doesn't need
عائلة لو لا تحتاج
a stupid son like you.
ابن غبي مثلك.
Haimeng.
هايمنغ.
Look outside.
أنظر إلى الخارج.
Do you want to...
هل تريد أن...
Just drive.
فقط قم بالقيادة.
[Cloud Manor]
[قصر السحاب]
You should go.
ينبغي عليك أن تذهب.
Where should I go?
أين يجب أن أذهب؟
Go home with your family,
اذهب إلى منزلك مع عائلتك،
or go back to your archery club.
أو العودة إلى نادي الرماية الخاص بك.
Either is fine.
أيهما جيد.
Don't wait anymore.
لا تنتظر أكثر.
But...
لكن...
She won't see you.
إنها لن تراك.
Lu Sinan's funeral is
جنازة لو سينان
already over.
لقد انتهى بالفعل.
Cloud Manor and Mare Nubium
قصر السحاب وبحر السحاب
have successfully returned
لقد عادوا بنجاح
to Haimeng's hands.
إلى أيدي هايمينج.
She's taken back
لقد تم إرجاعها
everything she wanted.
كل ما أرادته.
She will have nothing to do with the Lu family
لن يكون لها أي علاقة بعائلة لو
or anyone from the Lu family
أو أي شخص من عائلة لو
ever again.
مرة أخرى.
I want to see her.
أريد أن أراها.
I already told you...
لقد قلت لك بالفعل...
I want to see her!
أريد أن أراها!
I don't care what her relationship
لا يهمني ما هي علاقتها
with the Lu family is,
مع عائلة لو،
or whether she is
أو ما إذا كانت
an enemy or a foe of the Lu family.
عدو أو عدو لعائلة لو.
I want to see her!
أريد أن أراها!
♪ The wind blows softly ♪
♪ تهب الرياح بهدوء ♪
♪ I chase closely ♪
♪ أنا أطارد عن كثب ♪
♪ It rains all night ♪
♪ تمطر طوال الليل ♪
♪ Days pass by like this ♪
♪ تمر الأيام هكذا ♪
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪من أنا بالنسبة لك؟ ♪
♪ I'm tired too ♪
♪ أنا متعب أيضًا ♪
♪ But tell me why ♪
♪ ولكن قل لي لماذا ♪
♪ Why do I have to ♪
♪ لماذا يجب علي أن ♪
♪ Keep trapped in this cycle? ♪
♪ هل ستبقى عالقا في هذه الدورة؟ ♪
♪ I still can't let go of you ♪
♪ لا أزال لا أستطيع التخلي عنك ♪
♪ Carrying this weight inside ♪
♪ تحمل هذا الوزن في الداخل ♪
♪ Even if I never hear from you again ♪
♪ حتى لو لم أسمع منك مرة أخرى ♪
♪ Watch a movie ♪
♪ شاهد فيلمًا ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
♪أنا هنا ♪
♪ Those sweet words were not meant for me ♪
♪ تلك الكلمات الحلوة لم تكن موجهة لي ♪
♪ I still can't let go of you ♪
♪ لا أزال لا أستطيع التخلي عنك ♪
♪ And it's not such a pity ♪
♪وليس هذا أمر مؤسف ♪
♪ Actually, I won't push myself too hard ♪
♪ في الواقع، لن أضغط على نفسي كثيرًا ♪
♪ Scrolling through the messages ♪
♪ التمرير عبر الرسائل ♪
♪ Closing my eyes ♪
♪أغلق عيني ♪
♪ Good morning ♪
♪ صباح الخير ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ مم ♪
♪ Carry on ♪
♪استمر ♪
♪ Who am I to you? ♪
♪من أنا بالنسبة لك؟ ♪
♪ I'm tired too ♪
♪ أنا متعب أيضًا ♪
♪ But tell me why ♪
♪ ولكن قل لي لماذا ♪
♪ Why do I have to ♪
♪ لماذا يجب علي أن ♪
♪ Keep trapped in this cycle? ♪
♪ هل ستبقى عالقا في هذه الدورة؟ ♪
♪ I still can't let go of you ♪
♪ لا أزال لا أستطيع التخلي عنك ♪
♪ Lying to myself ♪
♪ أكذب على نفسي ♪
♪ Pretending we were still together that year ♪
♪ نتظاهر بأننا مازلنا معًا في ذلك العام ♪
♪ I'm here ♪
♪أنا هنا ♪
♪ Sing it to you ♪
♪ غنها لك ♪
♪ You asked if I could write a song for you ♪
♪ لقد سألتني إذا كان بإمكاني كتابة أغنية لك ♪